FRONTEND

DEVELOPER

# THIET HOANG KIEN





079 862-4951



hkthiet99@gmail.com

# INTRODUTION

Fourth-year student in Software Engineering at Ton Duc Thang University. Aiming to use my knowledge to experience in a dynamic, professional environment. From there, improve my knowledge, personal skills, working attitude and contribute to the company's benefits.

# **EDUCATION**

TON DUC THANG UNIVERSITY - (2017-2022) - HO CHI MINH CITY **BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING** 

Current GPA: 6.91

# EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - (SEP. 2021 - NOV. 2021) **CARP TECH CORPORATION** – Ho Chi Minh City

Working onsite at Asia Comercial Bank, participate in the React Boilerplate project - a website that specifies ACB's Components and build functionalities according to customer requirements.

**COMPUTER TECHNICIAN-** (JUNE. 2018 – OCT. 2018) FIX AND CARE – Ton Duc Thang University, Ho Chi Minh City

Supporting to repair computers, installing and guiding to use software.

# CERTIFICATE

SERVER-SIDE DEVELOPMENT WITH NODEJS, EXPRESS AND **MONGODB - (ACHIEVED AUG 08 2021)** 

Check it out: https://bit.ly/2VDi7lQ and my GitHub repository: https://bit.ly/3yxmVrA

# SKILLS

# # Python

The most familiar programming language proven by projects I have worked on related to AI, ML

#### # Javascript

Familiarity with ES6 and syntaxes through working directly with web application development

### # HTML & CSS

Basic skills and knowledge trained at the university with the background of working with web application development.

# # ReactJS

Familiarity with ReactJS using the Material UI and Ant Design library for my projects web application. Have basic knowledge to learn and work with ReactJS

#### # NodeJS

Understanding of API Communications and NodeJS frameworks such as ExpressJS, Socket.io, Mocha. Knowledge of database management and application security

#### # ExpressJS

Always use ExpressJS on the server-side for my web applications. Basic knowledge and be able to develop ExpressJS applications

# **PROJECTS**

ACB REACT BOILERPLATE - (SEP. 2021 – NOV. 2021)

**TECHNOLOGY USED:** ReactJS, Ant Design

The role of building layouts for websites such as Login Page, Landing Page, Components Page and embedding the ACB's Components, specifying them according to customer requirements.

# E-COMMERCE WEBSITE - (MAY. 2021 – SEP. 2021)

**TECHNOLOGY USED:** NodeJS, MongoDB, ReactJS, ExpressJS, Mocha & Chai, NYC Coverage reporter, Swagger API Specification, Docker Compose

- Developing a web application for merchants. The application helps users manage their personal information and list of products.
- Using JWT token authentication user based on RSA SHA-256 mechanism and login authorization for Facebook, Google. There are also features send emails for user using Nodemailer module.
- CRUD features to manage list of products.
- Sign-in, Sign-up, Sign-out and User Profile for manage user information.
- Making HTTP calls using Axios and calling multipart API with file upload.
- Using ExpressJS on the server-side and MongoDB for database management.
- Using ReactJS with Material UI library on the client-side.
- API Specification using Swagger 2.0.
- Unit testing for API using Mocha & Chai and NYC for Coverage reporter.
- Built Docker Compose for the API, Database and working on how to deploy a complete application.

**Github**: https://github.com/smoothkt4951/KT-Ecommerce

# RESEARCH

MASSIVE DATA PROCESSING - (MAR. 2021 – MAY. 2021)
TECHNOLOGY USED: Python, Jupyter Notebook, Machine Learning, PySpark.

- Researching about Massive Data Processing and synthesized as an instrumental study at GitHub.
- Finding Similar Documents Application with Locality Sensitive Hashing in Big Data.
- Machine Learning in PySpark and Recommendation System.

# MongoDB, SQL Server

My applications all use MongoDB.
Can develop and manage a basic
database and use my knowledge
about MongoDB, SQL Server to learn
and work with database
management.

# **#API Specifications**

Using Swagger to describe the API in my web application I am developing.

# # Unit Testing

Can write unit testing for the API using Mocha framework and Chai library and unit testing for the Components using JestJS framework, then using NYC for Coverage reporter. Can learn and work with the basic software testing process.

#### # Docker

Researching about Containerization on Docker, Google Kubernetes for distributed application deployment. Basic about build and run applications with Docker Compose. Knowledge of the syntax, architecture of Docker and using Portainer to deploy and manage the state of individual containers

#### # GitHub, GitLab

Working with GitLab at Asia Comercial Bank and familiarity with GitHub proven: https://github.com/smoothkt4951/

# **SOFT SKILLS**

#### # English

Reading documents, basic communication, email or report

# Teamwork

# Wri ting and presentations skills

# Sustainable development skills

**GitHub**: https://github.com/smoothkt4951/Massive-Data-Processing-Course